Guide to the Rice University President David W. Leebron Inauguration records, 2004-2006 UA 103
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series V: Testimonials (Boxes 6-10), 240896
  - University of the Incarnate Word, 240922 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of the South, 240921 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of Toledo, 240920 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of Tulsa, 240919 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of Vermont, 240918 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of Virginia, 240917 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of Wales, 240916 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of Wisconsin, Madison, 240915 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of Zurich, 240914 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Utah State University, 240913 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Vanderbilt University, 240912 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Vassar College, 240911 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University, 240910 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Waseda University, 240909 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Washington State University, 240908 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Washington University in St. Louis, 240907 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Western Michigan University, 240906 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Western Washington University, 240905 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - West Texas A&M University, 240904 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Wilson College, 240903 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Wittenberg University, 240902 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Wright State University, 240901 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Yale University, 240900 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - Yeshiva University, 240899 (Box 10, Folder -)
  - University of Houston, 240898 (Box OV, Folder -)
  - University of Montreal, 240897 (Box OV, Folder -)
- Series VI: Leebron Inaugural books, 240893
  - Hard-bound copies of the 2006 publication "The Inauguration of David W. Leebron: The Beginning of His Presidency of Rice University", 240895 (Box 11-18)
  - Online publication of "The Inauguration of David W. Leebron: The Beginning of his Presidency of Rice University" 2006, 240894
- Series VII: Inaugural Committee Documents Addendum, 240882
  - Inauguration Committee Documents (CD), 2004; 240892 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Budget, 2004; 240891 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Commemorative book materials, 240890 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Inaugural Committee administrative documents, 2004; 240889 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Inaugural events and invitations, 2004; 240888 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Inauguration expenses, 2004 - 2006; 240887 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Inauguration schedules, 2004; 240886 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Mailing lists, 2004; 240885 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Friday staff reception - photographs, 2004; 240884 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Friday cocktail reception - photographs, 2004; 240883 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Photographs: Inauguration of President Leebron, Leebron family (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Photographs: Inauguration, procession; faculty, staff reception at Cohen House; reception at Warwick; Autry Court (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: Inauguration, Autry Court; Lunch Reception, Hilton Americas; Dinner Reception, Warwick (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Photographs: Inauguration, Leebron family (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Photographs: Summons (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: Ceremony (Box 21, Folder 3-6)
  - Photographs: Alumni/Student Reception (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: Saturday Luncheon (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: Sunday Dinner (Box 21, Folder 9-10)
  - Photographs: Inauguration, multiple events (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - 15" x 20" summons-to-investiture document for David W. Leebron 10/2/2004 with Rice crest (Box 22, Item 1-8)
  - Congratulatory certificate from University of Houston on Leebron investiture (Box 22, Item 9)
  - Congratulatory certificate from Universite de Montreal on Leebron investiture (Box 22, Item 10)